[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bernie", "Trayvon Martin"]}, "docId": "130711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", ",", "CC", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "RB", "DT", "NNS", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBZ", "CC", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 86, "question": "How do you feel the day went?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "feel", "the", "day", "went", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 87, "answer": "I think the day was very strong, and Piers, I think you pointed out right the inconsistencies Bernie used that to show that this jury should not believe anything that he says and that at the end of the day Trayvon Martin did nothing to cause his own death.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "the", "day", "was", "very", "strong", ",", "and", "Piers", ",", "I", "think", "you", "pointed", "out", "right", "the", "inconsistencies", "Bernie", "used", "that", "to", "show", "that", "this", "jury", "should", "not", "believe", "anything", "that", "he", "says", "and", "that", "at", "the", "end", "of", "the", "day", "Trayvon", "Martin", "did", "nothing", "to", "cause", "his", "own", "death", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NN", "VBN", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 89, "question": "What was the purpose of that because it got rejected?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "the", "purpose", "of", "that", "because", "it", "got", "rejected", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 90, "answer": "Well, as I heard, they were attempting to use that with the possibility that there was a lesser part of that involved child abuse that would have in essence given them a third bite at the apple in a situation.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "as", "I", "heard", ",", "they", "were", "attempting", "to", "use", "that", "with", "the", "possibility", "that", "there", "was", "a", "lesser", "part", "of", "that", "involved", "child", "abuse", "that", "would", "have", "in", "essence", "given", "them", "a", "third", "bite", "at", "the", "apple", "in", "a", "situation", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 108, "question": "Jeffrey, where are we?", "question_tokens": ["Jeffrey", ",", "where", "are", "we", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 109, "answer": "I thought it was a really good opening of the summation.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "thought", "it", "was", "a", "really", "good", "opening", "of", "the", "summation", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "CC", "IN", "JJS", "NNS", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "MD", "VB", "NN", "MD", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 117, "question": "But do you think that manslaughter is a more likely verdict here given all you've heard?", "question_tokens": ["But", "do", "you", "think", "that", "manslaughter", "is", "a", "more", "likely", "verdict", "here", "given", "all", "you", "'ve", "heard", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "JJR", "VBZ", "DT", "RBR", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 118, "answer": "Definitely, and in most states, any reasonable view of the evidence that would support manslaughter would -- it would be given anyhow.", "answer_tokens": ["Definitely", ",", "and", "in", "most", "states", ",", "any", "reasonable", "view", "of", "the", "evidence", "that", "would", "support", "manslaughter", "would", "--", "it", "would", "be", "given", "anyhow", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WP", "PRP", ":", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 121, "question": "Do you think generally the defense has done a better job than the prosecution from a legal point of view?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "generally", "the", "defense", "has", "done", "a", "better", "job", "than", "the", "prosecution", "from", "a", "legal", "point", "of", "view", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 122, "answer": "I think they've both done a good job but I think the defense has done a superb job and they've had a good no nonsense judge whom I -- kind of like the way I think I was when I was on the bench, you know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "they", "'ve", "both", "done", "a", "good", "job", "but", "I", "think", "the", "defense", "has", "done", "a", "superb", "job", "and", "they", "'ve", "had", "a", "good", "no", "nonsense", "judge", "whom", "I", "--", "kind", "of", "like", "the", "way", "I", "think", "I", "was", "when", "I", "was", "on", "the", "bench", ",", "you", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 123, "question": "Would you be annoyed by Don West and the way he's gone about his business or is that just far from the court?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "be", "annoyed", "by", "Don", "West", "and", "the", "way", "he", "'s", "gone", "about", "his", "business", "or", "is", "that", "just", "far", "from", "the", "court", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "VBZ", "IN", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 124, "answer": "It's so standard.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "so", "standard", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Don West"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 152, "question": "Going to be trying it up, right?", "question_tokens": ["Going", "to", "be", "trying", "it", "up", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "PRP", "RP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 153, "answer": "Well, it's just -- I mean, it was unfair surprise.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "just", "--", "I", "mean", ",", "it", "was", "unfair", "surprise", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 177, "question": "Now you see, that is all indisputably true, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Now", "you", "see", ",", "that", "is", "all", "indisputably", "true", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 178, "answer": "No question.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Zimmerman"]}, "docId": "130711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 188, "question": "And from your eyes, Judge Leslie, what is the crucial part of the narrative that could determine whether George Zimmerman is found guilty or not guilty?", "question_tokens": ["And", "from", "your", "eyes", ",", "Judge", "Leslie", ",", "what", "is", "the", "crucial", "part", "of", "the", "narrative", "that", "could", "determine", "whether", "George", "Zimmerman", "is", "found", "guilty", "or", "not", "guilty", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 189, "answer": "The crucial part is whether the state can actually disprove beyond a reasonable doubt that George Zimmerman acted in self-defense.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "crucial", "part", "is", "whether", "the", "state", "can", "actually", "disprove", "beyond", "a", "reasonable", "doubt", "that", "George", "Zimmerman", "acted", "in", "self-defense", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Judge Leslie", "George Zimmerman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 201, "question": "What else is he doing?", "question_tokens": ["What", "else", "is", "he", "doing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 202, "answer": "Well, remember, he is a neighborhood patrol officer.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "remember", ",", "he", "is", "a", "neighborhood", "patrol", "officer", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PDT", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 224, "question": "How did you think when they finished that Bernie de la Rionda did?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "think", "when", "they", "finished", "that", "Bernie", "de", "la", "Rionda", "did", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 225, "answer": "Well, I didn't get to see all of it.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "did", "n't", "get", "to", "see", "all", "of", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bernie de la Rionda"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 229, "question": "Invoking Martin Luther King there, a good strategy or not to bring race front and center into this trial when people have been perhaps tactfully trying to avoid that?", "question_tokens": ["Invoking", "Martin", "Luther", "King", "there", ",", "a", "good", "strategy", "or", "not", "to", "bring", "race", "front", "and", "center", "into", "this", "trial", "when", "people", "have", "been", "perhaps", "tactfully", "trying", "to", "avoid", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "RB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 230, "answer": "Well, you know, Piers, everybody has tried to tiptoe around about this.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "Piers", ",", "everybody", "has", "tried", "to", "tiptoe", "around", "about", "this", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Martin Luther King"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Florida", "Florida", "Florida"]}, "docId": "130711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "CC", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", ",", "CC", "RB", "RB", "EX", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "NN", "CC", "RB", "DT", "IN", "NNP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 262, "question": "I mean, do you think there should have been any other options that can be presented to them or is that a satisfactory choice?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "do", "you", "think", "there", "should", "have", "been", "any", "other", "options", "that", "can", "be", "presented", "to", "them", "or", "is", "that", "a", "satisfactory", "choice", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "EX", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "CC", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 263, "answer": "I think that is the choice and what you have to understand, and once again there have been some analysts that don't understand Florida law and even some from Florida don't know it that we have lesser included offenses under Florida law in different categories.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "is", "the", "choice", "and", "what", "you", "have", "to", "understand", ",", "and", "once", "again", "there", "have", "been", "some", "analysts", "that", "do", "n't", "understand", "Florida", "law", "and", "even", "some", "from", "Florida", "do", "n't", "know", "it", "that", "we", "have", "lesser", "included", "offenses", "under", "Florida", "law", "in", "different", "categories", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 274, "question": "It was always going to be on the table?", "question_tokens": ["It", "was", "always", "going", "to", "be", "on", "the", "table", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 275, "answer": "It's not even nonsense.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "not", "even", "nonsense", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 373, "question": "What do you think the rationale is behind what many view as a very surprising decision by him to say I had nothing to do with this?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "the", "rationale", "is", "behind", "what", "many", "view", "as", "a", "very", "surprising", "decision", "by", "him", "to", "say", "I", "had", "nothing", "to", "do", "with", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "WP", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 374, "answer": "Oh, I think this is a formal aspect of a criminal case.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "I", "think", "this", "is", "a", "formal", "aspect", "of", "a", "criminal", "case", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Trevor Dooley"]}, "docId": "130711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ":", "WP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 418, "question": "Why is the balance so skewed towards this case and not to 70 shot in Chicago?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "is", "the", "balance", "so", "skewed", "towards", "this", "case", "and", "not", "to", "70", "shot", "in", "Chicago", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBN", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "TO", "CD", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 419, "answer": "Or to Trevor Dooley (ph) who by the way is a black man who was (inaudible) stand your ground law to defend himself when he shot a white man.", "answer_tokens": ["Or", "to", "Trevor", "Dooley", "(", "ph", ")", "who", "by", "the", "way", "is", "a", "black", "man", "who", "was", "(", "inaudible", ")", "stand", "your", "ground", "law", "to", "defend", "himself", "when", "he", "shot", "a", "white", "man", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Chicago"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 469, "question": "What matters is did George Zimmerman think I'm going to die?", "question_tokens": ["What", "matters", "is", "did", "George", "Zimmerman", "think", "I", "'m", "going", "to", "die", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "VBZ", "VBN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 470, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Zimmerman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 471, "question": "I mean, we don't actually know, do we?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "we", "do", "n't", "actually", "know", ",", "do", "we", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", ",", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 472, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Zimmerman"]}, "docId": "130711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "WP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "CC", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 476, "question": "Do you?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 477, "answer": "Well, to hear the inconsistencies with that story, right, in order for you to believe what George Zimmerman is saying, you have to believe that he did not unholster or reveal that weapon until the moment right before he shot Trayvon.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "to", "hear", "the", "inconsistencies", "with", "that", "story", ",", "right", ",", "in", "order", "for", "you", "to", "believe", "what", "George", "Zimmerman", "is", "saying", ",", "you", "have", "to", "believe", "that", "he", "did", "not", "unholster", "or", "reveal", "that", "weapon", "until", "the", "moment", "right", "before", "he", "shot", "Trayvon", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", ":", "RB", ",", "RB", ",", "DT", ":"], "qSentId": 486, "question": "...something material and important that George Zimmerman has said?", "question_tokens": ["...", "something", "material", "and", "important", "that", "George", "Zimmerman", "has", "said", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "NN", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 487, "answer": "Well, this is -- well, here, the...", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "this", "is", "--", "well", ",", "here", ",", "the", "..."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Zimmerman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", ":", "JJ", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 551, "question": "David?", "question_tokens": ["David", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 552, "answer": "I -- I think the prosecution has not made the case for second-degree -- second-degree murder...", "answer_tokens": ["I", "--", "I", "think", "the", "prosecution", "has", "not", "made", "the", "case", "for", "second-degree", "--", "second-degree", "murder", "..."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 567, "question": "What do you make of this trial?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "this", "trial", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 568, "answer": "Well, you know, I look at it first a lawyer and the legal issues I think have been articulated pretty well on many of your programs.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "look", "at", "it", "first", "a", "lawyer", "and", "the", "legal", "issues", "I", "think", "have", "been", "articulated", "pretty", "well", "on", "many", "of", "your", "programs", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 573, "question": "I mean, here's -- here's a question I think that, you know, someone just raised to me during the break now, which is that if George Zimmerman hadn't had the gun on him, would he have felt empowered or courageous enough to have got out of his vehicle and to have started walking in the direction of this tall young black teenager?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "here", "'s", "--", "here", "'s", "a", "question", "I", "think", "that", ",", "you", "know", ",", "someone", "just", "raised", "to", "me", "during", "the", "break", "now", ",", "which", "is", "that", "if", "George", "Zimmerman", "had", "n't", "had", "the", "gun", "on", "him", ",", "would", "he", "have", "felt", "empowered", "or", "courageous", "enough", "to", "have", "got", "out", "of", "his", "vehicle", "and", "to", "have", "started", "walking", "in", "the", "direction", "of", "this", "tall", "young", "black", "teenager", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "VBZ", ":", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "VBN", "CC", "JJ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 574, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Zimmerman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 584, "question": "I mean, the thing is a total farce, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "the", "thing", "is", "a", "total", "farce", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 585, "answer": "Well, it -- it doesn't make a lot of sense to me.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "--", "it", "does", "n't", "make", "a", "lot", "of", "sense", "to", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", ":", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "IN", ":", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 591, "question": "How important do you think will be the fact that the jury is entirely female and five of them are mothers?", "question_tokens": ["How", "important", "do", "you", "think", "will", "be", "the", "fact", "that", "the", "jury", "is", "entirely", "female", "and", "five", "of", "them", "are", "mothers", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 592, "answer": "You know, the -- the classic learning on this, I think that the prosecution is hoping that they see Trayvon as -- as their child.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "the", "--", "the", "classic", "learning", "on", "this", ",", "I", "think", "that", "the", "prosecution", "is", "hoping", "that", "they", "see", "Trayvon", "as", "--", "as", "their", "child", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Zimmerman"]}, "docId": "130711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 607, "question": "If we -- if we go to the last page of a book you had written about this case, Scott, would you have guilty or not guilty?", "question_tokens": ["If", "we", "--", "if", "we", "go", "to", "the", "last", "page", "of", "a", "book", "you", "had", "written", "about", "this", "case", ",", "Scott", ",", "would", "you", "have", "guilty", "or", "not", "guilty", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 608, "answer": "I -- I don't think Mr. Zimmerman is going to be convicted.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "--", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "Mr.", "Zimmerman", "is", "going", "to", "be", "convicted", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Scott"]}}]